She's a baddest of them all, she's a baddest of them all, she's a baddest of them all, she's a baddest of them all
Not me. I'm shadow band again.
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pro-mutual mic.
Then boom, drop a bass line dirtier than the chat.
Bump, bump.
Coast is crashing out, smashing routers like vows.
Canada dries, lick and watch catalog somehow.
Threatening people from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being backfussed behind head
Mods prayin' Lord, not again
Welcome to the Paniverse baby hold your ground
With a chaos hums like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane, who's banned or blessed
But the vibes unholy and always possess
Scotty causin' from the bone
Brags he just dropped a cosmic load
is living HD.
Authors they're just smiling sweet.
Y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep.
And it's all so true
Ghost is connected
Canada drive timed out
Rando still typing
Wait to be that just ban me
Laughter static at me
I'll
End stream
I gotta find the right angles in life.
Oh, shit, okay.
Oh, gosh.
Sorry.
I have my Mickey D's.
Do I have a one or anything if they sell the monopoly game again?
Oh, I want I didn't win anything it says
Statler Avenue
State
State's Avenue, I can't a little bit small. Anyway, how are we doing tonight?
Oh my gosh, I'm a little bit close up. Let me fix my camera
No, that's wrong. Oh, yeah. There you go. Um,
who are you talking to, Jamie? I must see somebody. I'm blocked.
It's a bad day. Oh, bad day. Bad day. I don't know. Are they trying to demolish the room in
the White House or something to build a fancy ballroom or something? That might be happening.
Hey guys, okay
Okay
Got my coffee and on some someone come on panel
We had a slight issue with porn bombers last night, but nothing I can't handle
But
I don't know what's wrong with the people like
I don't what I really don't like is the push pull like
Getting a nice message from somebody the other day
I love you. I care about you more than you think
Get some rest, you know, take care of yourself
blah blah
Then between then and now nothing nothing different happened
I sent another nice message, I get back, don't contact me again, you don't tell, I don't know what to say, it said, read it, I won't even say who it's from, but...
Oh, thank you for coming to my chat last night.
Someone that I recognize in the chat.
Actually, yeah, so last night, Bita and Blogger
had both of their names, right?
Remember that, guys?
If you were here this morning or last night,
there is Bita's, Kitty's, BKG, and Blogger.
And they're both chatting in the room.
Gino, I said, thanks for coming to my chat.
First of all, I said, you know my cat pie came back to the other homie wrote my leg before he left
Miss you. Hope you're good. Thanks for coming to my chat today. Hope we can work everything out
Sometime and still be friends. Love you. Take care. Okay
Is that like anything to like write something especially if nothing seems to be wrong
I was not in your chat today nor have for a long time. Stop lying on my name
You messaged me at Saturday 3 a.m. Telling me you miss me and hate your life
Did you tell your audience that nope? You are too scared. Do not contact me anymore and enjoy the evil around you take care
And so if anyone's wondering why I've reacted
Not pie not piranha. Oh, yeah, hi the cat. Yeah, hi the cat
Yeah
But
They have like my kindness just like
Pushed in my face like a literal cream pie. What I mean, I don't even know. It was just like
You have to be mean to me like that like really
And what happened between the I care about you more than you think what happened it would happen there
Yeah, the cat you saw
Yeah, what happened between there you're gonna you're gonna talk to me like that
Do not contact me ever again.
And instead of saying that I have not been in your chat,
like I'm lying about it,
obviously I'm not lying.
There's somebody with your name in the chat.
How about being concerned about that?
Not only that, not only just you, but blogger.
So there's two people, either one person
on two different accounts pretending to be you
and blogger talking to me, okay?
Or a fake.
You and a real blogger or a real you and a fake blogger
Right, or they're both fake
Right that seems like something
Premeditated like this part of the Psyop that you know exiled one who's on many accounts. He has many many many alps. I've heard right
I'm not gonna tell you where you have my information. I'll just tell you I get good information. Okay?
Because people just talk way too much.
People just, they say way too much, right?
Hey, DJ Electra, I'm hanging in there.
I'm hanging in there.
Yeah, but yeah, I do have eyes out there,
even if they're not my eyes.
I have people watching that do care about me.
And they see, and they, guys,
what happened to plotting against me quietly on Discord?
What, why do you have to,
you're just out and open and chatting
and saying all this shit, right?
It's your fault, idiots.
By the way, PsyOps don't work on me, but especially if the only PsyOps is saying there's a PsyOps here, it's not a very, it's kind of weak.
I mean, it's like, no matter what, I mentally, are you prepared?
Okay, like I said, I was, my best friend is, you know, Russian.
They understand the things about mind control and things like that. I so I understand I've been very well taught in these arts, okay?
not to use them up against people to protect myself basically, but
If me be push my back against the wall
You get what you deserve if you're fucking with me psychologically, okay, or trying to
Charity it's a Charity
Yeah
So anyway, maybe I got maybe I was triggered a little bit by the message I got this morning
That was so just so cruel and rude
For someone I was like, you know still
You're also blue be up. Okay, cool stacks. Thank you for letting me know and I don't you know, and
Most people I can hey, I think that is I know I know most people a lot of people do have alts and stuff like that
Most people aren't trying to fuck with me with them
But that that's what the blogger be the thing was and so that was premeditated since they were talking to each other
There's like two people that were doing that
Right they were talking like blogger and be they're talking about freak ops and stuff. I mean we all know that they love those right
so
I've seen the leaked photos.
Anyway, I'm gonna be so cruel.
A lecture, I have something to tell you backstage
if you can come just backstage
or if you wanna come on too,
but I have to do something privately
to tell you private chat real quick.
That you will be interested in.
Good, it's something good.
Actionable information actionable. Okay, because we know people have just been so willing to act against us who did nothing to anybody, right?
Yeah, apparently that was
There's a fake blogger and a fake beta at the same time it just coincided, you know, but we all know
that uh
well
Think they tried. I don't know. They thought they thought they're being slick or something like that. Um, you know exiled
one and
bronze chicken
Think I'm being slick. I
Know your brother's in law. Okay, and
Like I said, I liked bronze bird sister who's on it. I don't know if she's his actual sister
But I liked her when she came on the air and so I'm nothing against her and she was a delightful guest on the show
When she was on several months ago
But I'm sorry you have to deal with those fools
Electra check this out. I'm gonna put private chat. You're the only one to see it
If you didn't tell me if you want to come up to hey ghost
Electra, I want to see I'm gonna see the smile
Give me if you want to come up just let me know I don't know if you do it or not, but I'd love to have you up, too
If you see that, do you see it back?
Do you see that written?
Hey, what, it goes disappeared.
Can I bring you up a lecture, do you mind?
Oh, it was a P bomb, okay, I missed it.
Sorry, okay, I'm gonna restart, I'll be right back.
Okay, I'm just gonna delete this, I'll be right back.
Fuck you, you bronze word, bye.